<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kdeconnect</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KDE-Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE-anslut</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Connectxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE 連線</name>
  <summary>Seamless connection of your devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Connexió transparent amb els vostres dispositius</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Connexió transparent amb els vostres dispositius</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Nahtlose Verbindung zu Ihren Geräten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Seamless connection of your devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Conexión sin interrupciones de sus dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Connecter vos périphériques avec facilité</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Conexión transparente entre dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Koneksi yang mulus terhadap perangkat-perangkatmu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Connessione trasparente dei tuoi dispositivi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">장치와 항상 연결하기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Vientisas jūsų įrenginių sujungimas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Naadloze verbinding met uw apparaten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zintegrowane połączenia do twoich urządzeń</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Ligação transparente aos seus dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Conexão transparente com seus dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Jednoduché prepojenie vašich zariadení</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Sömlös anslutning av dina apparater</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Зручне з'єднання із вашими пристроями</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSeamless connection of your devicesxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">無縫連結您的裝置</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KDE Connect provides several features to integrate your phone and your computer:
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDE Connect proporciona diverses característiques per integrar el telèfon i l'ordinador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KDE Connect proporciona diverses característiques per integrar el telèfon i l'ordinador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KDE-Connect bietet mehrere Funktionen zur Integration Ihres Telefons und Ihres Rechners:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Connect provides several features to integrate your phone and your computer:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDE Connect proporciona varias funcionalidades para integrar su teléfono y su equipo:</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KDE Connect fornece varias funcionalidades para integrar o teléfono co computador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KDE Connect menyediakan fitur-fitur untuk mengintegrasikan ponselmu dan komputermu:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDE Connect fornisce diverse funzioni per integrare il tuo telefono e il tuo computer:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDE Connect는 컴퓨터와 휴대폰을 통합하는 여러 기능을 제공합니다:</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">KDE Connect pateikia kelias ypatybes, skirtas integruoti jūsų telefoną ir kompiuterį:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Connect biedt verschillende functis om uw telefoon en uw computer te integreren:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KDE Connect zapewnia kilka możliwości zintegrowania telefonu z komputerem:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Connect oferece diversas funcionalidades para integrar o seu telefone com o seu computador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDE Connect oferece diversos recursos para integrar seu telefone com seu computador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KDE Connect poskytuje niekoľko funkcií na integráciu vášho telefónu s vašim počítačom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-anslut tillhandahåller integrering mellan en Android-telefon och skrivbordet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У KDE Connect реалізовано декілька можливостей з інтеграції вашого телефону і комп'ютера:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Connect provides several features to integrate your phone and your computer:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">《KDE 連線》提供多個功能，來整合您的手機及電腦：</p>
    <p>Please note you will need to install KDE Connect on your
    computer for this app to work, and keep the desktop version
    up-to-date with the Android version for the latest features to
    work.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Recordeu que cal instal·lar el KDE Connect a l'ordinador perquè aquesta aplicació funcioni, i mantenir actualitzada la versió de l'escriptori amb la versió d'Android perquè funcionin les últimes característiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Recordeu que cal instal·lar el KDE Connect a l'ordinador perquè aquesta aplicació funcione, i mantindre actualitzada la versió de l'escriptori amb la versió d'Android perquè funcionen les últimes característiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Bitte beachten Sie, dass Sie KDE-Connect auf Ihrem Rechner installieren müssen, damit diese App funktioniert. Halten Sie die Arbeitsflächen-Version und Android-Version auf dem neusten Stand, damit Sie die neuesten Funktionen nutzen können</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Please note you will need to install KDE Connect on your computer for this app to work, and keep the desktop version up-to-date with the Android version for the latest features to work.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Tenga en cuenta que tendrá que instalar KDE Connect en su equipo para que esta aplicación funcione, y tendrá que mantener la versión de escritorio actualizada con la versión de Android para que las últimas funcionalidades estén disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Teña en conta que terá que instalar KDE Connect no computador para que este aplicativo funcione, e manter a versión do escritorio actualizada con respecto á versión de Android para que as novas funcionalidades funcionen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Mohon diingat bahwa kamu perlu menginstal KDE Connect pada komputermu agar aplikasi ini bekerja, dan jaga versi desktop terupdate dengan versi Android supaya setidaknya fitur-fiturnya bekerja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Affinché questa applicazione funzioni dovrai installare KDE Connect sul tuo computer e mantenere la versione desktop aggiornata alla versione Android, in modo che le funzionalità più recenti siano attive.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 앱을 사용하려면 컴퓨터에 KDE Connect를 설치해야 하며, 최신 기능을 사용하려면 데스크톱과 안드로이드 버전을 항상 최신 버전으로 업데이트해야 합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Turėkite omenyje, jog tam, kad ši programėlė veiktų, jums reikės įdiegti KDE Connect savo kompiuteryje, o tam, kad veiktų naujausios ypatybės, turėsite palaikyti darbalaukio versiją kartu su Android versija atnaujintą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Merk op dat het nodig is om KDE Connect op uw computer te installeren om deze app te laten werken en de bureaubladversie up-to-date te houden met de Android-versie om de laatste functies te laten werken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Aby ta aplikacja zadziała, należy wgrać KDE Connect na komputerze i uaktualniać wersję na komputerze z tą na Androidzie, tak aby móc korzystać z najnowszych możliwości.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Lembre-se que terá de instalar o KDE Connect no seu computador para esta aplicação funcionar, e deve manter a versão do mesmo actualizada com a versão para Android, para que as últimas funcionalidades funcionem bem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Lembre-se de que é necessário instalar o KDE Connect no seu computador para este aplicativo funcionar e também manter a versão atualizada com a versão para Android, de forma que os recursos mais recentes funcionem bem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Pamätajte, že si musíte nainštalovať KDE Connect, aby fungovala táto aplikácia a udržiavať verziu pracovného prostredia aktuálnu s verziou Androidu, aby fungovali najnovšie funkcie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Observera att KDE-anslut måste installeras på datorn för att appen ska fungera, och att skrivbordsdatorns version måste hållas uppdaterad tillsammans med Androidversionen för att de senaste funktionerna ska fungera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Будь ласка, зауважте, що для того, щоб ця програма працювала, вам слід встановити KDE Connect на ваш комп'ютер і підтримувати синхронізацію версій із Android, щоб можна було скористатися найновішими можливостями.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxPlease note you will need to install KDE Connect on your computer for this app to work, and keep the desktop version up-to-date with the Android version for the latest features to work.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">請注意：您將需要在電腦上安裝《KDE 連線》才能使此 App 運作，並保持桌面版為 Android 版的最新版本，以讓最新功能能夠運作。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://community.kde.org/KDEConnect</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kdeconnect</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/index.php?application=kdeconnect-kde&amp;language=en</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/plasmoid.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/kcm.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/gnome3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
