<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kdeconnect</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE-anslut</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Connectxx</name>
  <summary>Seamless connection of your devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Connexió transparent amb els vostres dispositius</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Connexió transparent amb els vostres dispositius</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Seamless connection of your devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Connecter vos périphériques avec facilité</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Naadloze verbinding met uw apparaten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Ligação transparente aos seus dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Conexão transparente com seus dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Jednoduché prepojenie vašich zariadení</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Sömlös anslutning av dina apparater</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Зручне з'єднання із вашими пристроями</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSeamless connection of your devicesxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KDE Connect provides several features to integrate your phone and your computer:
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDE Connect proporciona diverses característiques per integrar el telèfon i l'ordinador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KDE Connect proporciona diverses característiques per integrar el telèfon i l'ordinador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Connect provides several features to integrate your phone and your computer:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Connect biedt verschillende functis om uw telefoon en uw computer te integreren:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Connect oferece diversas funcionalidades para integrar o seu telefone com o seu computador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDE Connect oferece diversos recursos para integrar seu telefone com seu computador:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KDE Connect poskytuje niekoľko funkcií na integráciu vášho telefónu s vašim počítačom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-anslut tillhandahåller integrering mellan en Android-telefon och skrivbordet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У KDE Connect реалізовано декілька можливостей з інтеграції вашого телефону і комп'ютера:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Connect provides several features to integrate your phone and your computer:xx</p>
    <p>Please note you will need to install KDE Connect on your
    computer for this app to work, and keep the desktop version
    up-to-date with the Android version for the latest features to
    work.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Recordeu que cal instal·lar el KDE Connect a l'ordinador perquè aquesta aplicació funcioni, i mantenir actualitzada la versió de l'escriptori amb la versió d'Android perquè funcionin les últimes característiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Recordeu que cal instal·lar el KDE Connect a l'ordinador perquè aquesta aplicació funcione, i mantindre actualitzada la versió de l'escriptori amb la versió d'Android perquè funcionen les últimes característiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Please note you will need to install KDE Connect on your computer for this app to work, and keep the desktop version up-to-date with the Android version for the latest features to work.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Merk op dat het nodig is om KDE Connect op uw computer te installeren om deze app te laten werken en de bureaubladversie up-to-date te houden met de Android-versie om de laatste functies te laten werken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Lembre-se que terá de instalar o KDE Connect no seu computador para esta aplicação funcionar, e deve manter a versão do mesmo actualizada com a versão para Android, para que as últimas funcionalidades funcionem bem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Lembre-se de que é necessário instalar o KDE Connect no seu computador para este aplicativo funcionar e também manter a versão atualizada com a versão para Android, de forma que os recursos mais recentes funcionem bem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Pamätajte, že si musíte nainštalovať KDE Connect, aby fungovala táto aplikácia a udržiavať verziu pracovného prostredia aktuálnu s verziou Androidu, aby fungovali najnovšie funkcie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Observera att KDE-anslut måste installeras på datorn för att appen ska fungera, och att skrivbordsdatorns version måste hållas uppdaterad tillsammans med Androidversionen för att de senaste funktionerna ska fungera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Будь ласка, зауважте, що для того, щоб ця програма працювала, вам слід встановити KDE Connect на ваш комп'ютер і підтримувати синхронізацію версій із Android, щоб можна було скористатися найновішими можливостями.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxPlease note you will need to install KDE Connect on your computer for this app to work, and keep the desktop version up-to-date with the Android version for the latest features to work.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://community.kde.org/KDEConnect</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kdeconnect</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/index.php?application=kdeconnect-kde&amp;language=en</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/plasmoid.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/kcm.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/gnome3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
